  const questionBank = [
    {
      question: 'In 1958, who designed the current flag with 50 stars and 13 stripes?',
      answerIndex: 2,
      answers: [
      'President Dwight D. Eisenhower',
      'Betsy Ross',
      'A high school student'],
      followup: 'A 17-year-old high school student, Robert G. Heft, had his design chosen out of 1,500 entries.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Is it ever appropriate to fly the flag upside down?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Yes', 'No'],
      followup: 'Yes, but only in an emergency. It means \"Help Me! It\'s an emergency! Call the police! I am in dire trouble and need immediate help!\"',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is an expert on flags called?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Vexillologist',
      'Chiropterologist',
      'Podiatrist'],
      followup: 'A vexillologist studies history, symbolism, and the usage of flags.',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many US flags are there on the moon?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['6', '4', '0'],
      followup: 'There are a total of 6 US flags on the moon of which 5 are standing while the first one hoisted by Neil Armstrong fell.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What day is Flag Day?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['June 14th',
      'July 4th',
      'Sept 21st'],
      followup: 'Flag Day is on June 14th. The holiday was developed by a school teacher and signed into law in 1949.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which one of these is NOT a nickname for The US flag?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Waving Stripes',
      'Stars and Stripes',
      'Star-Spangled Banner',
      'Old Glory'],
      followup: 'Stars and Stripes, Star-Spangled Banner, and Old Glory are all nicknames for the US flag.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What state became the 50th star on the US flag in 1960?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Hawaii',
      'Alaska',
      'New Mexico'],
      followup: 'In 1959, Hawaii was the last state admitted to the union.',
    },
    {
      question: 'True or false: The pledge of allegiance was written by Francis Scott Key?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['False', 'True'],
      followup: 'Francis Bellamy wrote the pledge of allegiance.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Over which fort, did the original star spangled banner, immortalized by Francis Scott Key, fly? ',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Fort McHenry',
      'Fort Ticonderoga',
      'Fort Sumter'],
      followup: 'Francis Scott Key observed the British bombardment of Fort McHenry in 1814 during the War of 1812.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Have there have been more than 15 official versions of the US flag?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Yes', 'No'],
      followup: 'There have been 27 official versions of the American flag, each with a different amount of stars.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the color blue symbolize on the US flag?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['loyalty', 'royalty', 'honor'],
      followup: 'History states that red, white and blue were chosen as the colors to represent valor (red), liberty and purity (white), and justice and loyalty (blue).',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is said to have made the first American flag?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Betsy Ross', 'Martha Washington', 'Martha Stewart', 'Betty Crocker'],
      followup: 'Although she purportedly sewed the first flag in 1776, Ross wasn\'t credited with this work during her lifetime.',
    },
    {
      question: 'The exact proportions of the flag arrangements of stars were not officially declared until a presidential order in ______?',
      answerIndex: 2,
      answers: ['1817', '1888', '1912', '1954'],
      followup: 'Executive Order of President Taft dated June 24, 1912 provided arrangement for the stars and stripes.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which officials are allowed to order the flag to be flown at half staff at government buildings?',
      answerIndex: 3,
      answers: ['President', 'Mayor', 'Governor', 'President and Governor'],
      followup: 'According to the Flag Code, only the President of the United States, your state\'s Governor, and the Mayor of the District of Columbia can order the US flag lowered to half-staff.',
    },
    {
      question: 'According to the U.S. Flag Code, which is the preferred way to take care of a flag that is tattered and no longer usable?',
      answerIndex: 2,
      answers: ['Recycle it', 'Bury it', 'Burn it', 'Send to State Capitol'],
      followup: 'The United States Flag Code states: "The Flag, when it is in such condition that it is no longer a fitting emblem of display, should be destroyed in a dignified way, preferably by burning.',
    },
    {
      question: 'National Flag Day was established to commemorate ____',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['The adoption of the U.S. Flag in 1777.', 'The birthday of Francis Scott Key.', 'The birthday of George Washington.'],
      followup: 'On May 30, 1916, President Woodrow Wilson issued a presidential proclamation establishing a national Flag Day on June 14.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What are the penalties for not complying with U.S. Flag Code.',
      answerIndex: 2,
      answers: ['Fine', 'Jail', 'No Penalty'],
      followup: 'The Flag Code has no provision for enforcement. No fines, no penalties. There is nothing law enforcement can do when the Flag Code is broken.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which one of these is NOT against the U.S. Flag Code?',
      answerIndex: 2,
      answers: ['Using the flag for advertising', 'Using the flag for clothing, bedding, or draperies', 'Using the flag for a flag pin'],
      followup: 'The flag should never be used for advertising purposes or embroidered on clothing or fabric.',
    },
    {
      question: 'According to the U.S. Flag Code, which of these are NOT in the guidelines?',
      answerIndex: 2,
      answers: ['The flag should not be dipped for any person or things except in special naval procedures.', 'The flag should not touch the ground.', 'The flag should never fly at night.'],
      followup: 'You can keep your flag flying 24-hours if it is properly illuminated during all hours of darkness.',
    },
    {
      question: 'According to the National Flag Code,  which of these are guidelines for those not in military uniform during the playing of the national anthem or the reciting of the Pledge of Allegiance?',
      answerIndex: 0,
      answers: ['Stand at attention with hand over heart.', 'Salute throughout', 'Rules are flexible depending on the time and place.'],
      followup: 'The code states that persons present are expected to stand and face the flag with right hand over heart.',
    },
  ];

  export function generateTrivia() {
    return questionBank[Math.floor(Math.random()*questionBank.length)];
  }
